const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。15×100＝', answer: '1500', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。632×100＝', answer: '63200', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。590×100＝', answer: '59000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。384×1000＝', answer: '384000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。120×1000＝', answer: '120000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。500×100＝', answer: '50000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。2800×100＝', answer: '280000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。1040×100＝', answer: '104000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。3000×1000＝', answer: '3000000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '暗算で計算しましょう。105×1000＝', answer: '105000', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];